https://huggableteddybears.com/privacy-policy.html

Last added items
Subtotal:
$0.00
View cart
Checkout
The order subtotal is less than the minimum allowed value ($4.00)
Jul 30, 2020
D-backs filled the seats with teddy bears for Phoenix Children’s Hospital
Huggable Teddy Bears sends Teddy Bears to help fill the seats at Chase field this week.
Jun 26, 2020
Reopen for business!
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting our web store.The site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these organizations for marketing purposes. We may also share information as part of a sale of all or part of the company.Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:By E-Mail: CustomerService@huggableteddybears.comBy Phone: 630-780-4273 We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used primarily to fulfill your specific request.
Sign up for Personalized Teddy Bears Gifts - Huggable Teddy Bears news
Email
*
Subscribe
Can't subscribe you right now. Try later
Thank you for subscribing to the newsletter! We hope you enjoy shopping at Personalized Teddy Bears Gifts - Huggable Teddy Bears
Contact us
20987 N John Wayne Pkwy, Suite #B-104-376, Maricopa, AZ, US, 85139
New!
© 2006 - 2020 Personalized Teddy Bears Gifts - Huggable Teddy Bears. All rights reserved.
Powered by X-Cart
